Guide to the David J. Skorton Presidential Liaison records, 2006-2014.
Skorton, David J. papers
- Series I. Meetings and Briefings
  - Breakfast with John Swanson (FUCHS), March 30, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Visit with Andrew, Jennifer and Marilyn Brice (FUCHS), April 3, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Harris Rosen, April 4, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bob Appel, April 9, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with George Gellert, April 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Hank Greenberg, April 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Tower Club Reception, April 11, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Phone calls to Alumni Trustee Candidates, April 11, 2012 (Box 7)
  - CALS Advisory Council Meeting (FUCHS), April 19, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Todd Glass (FUCHS), April 19, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Johnson Advisory Council Dinner (FUCHS), April 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with David and Pat Atkinson (FUCHS), April 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Irwin and Joan Jacobs Scholars Dinner (FUCHS), April 24, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Irwin and Joan Jacobs, April 24, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Parents Campus Visit, April 28, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jean Baderschneider, April 30, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Milstein Family Recognition Luncheon, May 12, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Visit with David Lederman (FUCHS), May 14, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Senior Class Final Reception, May 25, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Chuck Feeney, May 25, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Narayana and Rohan Murthy, May 29, 2012 (Box 7)
  - ICON of the Industry Awards, June 5, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Private mtg w/Tisch Family, June 5, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Phone call with Mike Zak, June 5, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Sam Fleming, June 6, 2012 (Box 7)
  - DVM Welcome Reception, June 7, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Phone call to Irwin Jacobs, June 7, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Combined Class Reception ’37, ’42, ‘47, June 7, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Cornell NYC Tech Presentation (FUCHS), June 8, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1947 Dinner (FUCHS), June 8, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’87 Reception, June 8, 2012 (Box 7)
  - CBAA Reception, June 8, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1962 Dinner, June 8, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Olin Lecture – Michelle Rhee, June 8, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Olin/Giving Reception (FUHCS), June 8, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Olin Luncheon, June 8, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Class of 2007 Reception, June 9, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1972 Dinner, June 9, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Cornelliana Night, June 9, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Law School Groundbreaking Ceremony, June 9, 2012 (Box 7)
  - State of the University Address, June 9, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with David Duffield (FUCHS), June 11, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Hank Greenberg, June 11, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Harold Tanner Prize Luncheon, June 15, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Mort Zuckerman, June 19, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Darren Walker, June 19, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Diana Taylor, July 9, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Ed Meyer, July 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Peter Wright, July 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with PCCW Leadership, July 11, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Phone call with Terry Lundgren, July 16, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Roy Park, July 19, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Mike Zak, July 26, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jim McCormick (FUCHS), August 2, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Legacy Reception, August 18, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Nantucket Reception and Dinner, August 30, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Michele Bachelet (FUCHS), September 4, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Bartels World Affairs Fellow Lecture (FUCHS), September 4, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Major Gifts Committee Meeting, September 5, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Chairman Circle Dinner, September 5, 2012 (Box 7)
  - PCAM Welcome, September 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Private Meeting with Presidential Councillors, September 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - PCAM: Monday Night Dinner, September 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jim and Becky Morgan (FUCHS), September 11, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Len and Fleur Harlan, September 14, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Private mtg w/Eric Schmidt, September 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Hatfield Lecture, September 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Hatfield Reception and Dinner, September 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - FHTR Awards, September 21, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Lynch Weiss Welcome, September 22, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Larry and Theresa Salameno, September 27, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Dr. James Simons, October 1, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Judith Rodin, October 3, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Christopher Oechsli, October 3, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jan Zubrow, October 3, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Dinner hosted by Bill and Linda Macaulay, October 4, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Ed Meyer, October 5, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Irwin Jacobs, October 12, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Dinner with Ratan Tata, October 12, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bo Hurlbut, October 15, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Kevin Glazer, October 15, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Rochester All Alumni Event, October 15, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with David and Barbara Zalaznick, October 17, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Tony Wang, October 18, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with John Megrue, October 18, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bob Harrison, October 18, 2012 (Box 7)
  - JGSM Advisory Council (FUCHS), October 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with K. B. Suh, October 22, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Richard and Lisa Baker, October 23, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Andrew Tisch, October 24, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Tata Trust Meeting, October 24, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Pete and Nancy Meinig, October 25, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Wine and Dine Event, October 25, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Martin Tang (FUCHS), October 25, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Joint Annual Meeting, October 26, 2012 (Box 7)
  - TCAM: Friday Night Dinner, October 26, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Cornell Annual Fund Breakfast, October 27, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Fred Young (FUCHS), November 6, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Nandlal Tolani and Family, November 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Visit with Ratan Tata, November 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - India All Alumni Reception, November 10, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Phone call with Armando Olivera, December 2012 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Andrew Tisch, December 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Phone call to David Duffield, December 20, 2012 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with David Zalaznick (FUCHS), January 10, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bob Appel, January 10, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Fisk Johnson, January 11, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Seth Klarman, January 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Mike Zak, January 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bob Langer, January 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with David Croll, January 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - CALC Luncheon, January 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Chuck Feeney, January 21, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bill Sanders (FUCHS), January 24, 2013 (Box 7)
  - President’s Circle Dinner, January 30, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Ratan Tata, February 1, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Sr. Class Spring Reception, February 4, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Hank Greenberg, February 14, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Reception hosted by Jeff and Julie Parker, February 15, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Investment Committee Meeting, February 16, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Bruch Cruise hosted by Lee and Mary Pillsbury, February 17, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Dinner hosted by David Skorton, February 17, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Jack Clarke, February 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Dinner hosted by Al and Betsey Harris, February 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Tata Trust Video Conference, February 22, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Phone call with John Xefox, February 25, 2013 (Box 7)
  - PCCW Friday Dinner, March 1, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Asia Leadership Conference Video Shoot, March 6, 2013 (Box 7)
  - San Francisco Campaign Event, March 12, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jim Morgans, March 13, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with George Gellert, March 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Anika Daniels-Osaze, March 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Len Harlan, March 21, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Andrew Tisch, March 21, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Mike Zak (FUCHS), March 27, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Dave and Pat Atkinson, April 8, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Dave and Pat Atkinson (FUCHS), April 8, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Spring Recognition Event, April 10, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Tom Groos, April 11, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with David Einhorn, April 11, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Ira Drukier, April 29, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bob Appel, April 29, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Girish Reddy, April 29, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Joan and Irwin Jacobs (FUCHS), April 29, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Semester Prize Lunch, May 6, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Doug Leone (FUCHS), May 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Carl Bass (FUCHS), May 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Skype with Dick Groos, May 21, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Visit with the Merrill Family, May 22, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Seth Klarman, May 23, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Klarman Hall Groundbreaking Ceremony, May 23, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Klarman Hall Groundbreaking Lunch, May 23, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Sr. Class Campaign Final Reception, May 24, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Fred Dombrose, June 5, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Classes of ’38, ’43, ’48 Combined Reception, June 6, 2013 (Box 7)
  - DVM Welcome Reception, June 6, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1973 Dinner, June 6, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Iroquois Social, June 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’63 Dinner, June 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’78 Dinner (FUCHS), June 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - CAAA Lunch (FUCHS), June 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Olin Lecture, June 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Giving Society Reception (FUCHS), June 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Class of 1988 Dinner, June 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’83 Reception, June 7, 2013 (Box 7)
  - State of the Univ. Address, June 8, 2013 (Box 7)
  - NYC Tech Campus Forum (FUCHS), June 8, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’68 Dinner (FUCHS), June 8, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Yossie Hollander, June 27, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Andrew Paul, July 1, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with John Dyson, July 2, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jim Simons, July 3, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Roy Park, July 9, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Fred Young, July 11, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Ed Meyers, July 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Andrew Tisch, August 29, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Library Campaign Event, September 10, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Major Gifts Committee Luncheon, September 11, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Lowell McAdam (FUCHS), September 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Hatfield Lecture (FUCHS), September 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Hatfield Reception and Dinner (FUCHS), September 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - FHTR Awards Dinner, September 20, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Big Red Band Dedication, September 21, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Lynch Weiss Welcome, September 21, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Miller Dinner, October 2, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with John Swanson (FUCHS), October 8, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jim McCormick (FUCHS), October 17, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Chicago Cornell Now 2015 All Alumni Event, October 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Lunch hosted by Bill Perez, October 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Martin Tang (FUCHS), October 24, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with David Croll, October 24, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Bush/Zimpher Panel, October 24, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Joint Annual Meeting, October 25, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Friday Reception and Dinner, October 25, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Higher Education Rising Costs: What Does the Future Hold? (FUCHS), October 25, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Annual Fund Breakfast, October 26, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bob Appel, October 30, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Girish Reddy, November 1, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Gara LaMarche, November 5, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Fred Young (FUCHS), November 8, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Tom Secunda, November 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Chris Oechsli, November 18, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Visit with Drs. Roy and Josephine Curtiss, November 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Andrew Tisch, November 19, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Rob Ryan and David Parker (FUCHS), November 20, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bobby Abrams, December 2, 2013 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Mike Goguen (FUCHS), January 8, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jim and Becky Morgan (FUCHS), January 8, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Doug Leone (FUCHS), January 8, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Ann Bowers (FUCHS), January 8, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Bruce Ratner, January 20, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bobby Abrams, January 20, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with PCCW Leadership, January 21, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Andy Paul, January 21, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Lunch mtg with Pete Meinig, January 29, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Major Gifts Committee Lunch Mtg (FUCHS), January 29, 2014 (Box 7)
  - President’s Circle Dinner, January 29, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Breakfast with Susan and Greg Gianforte (FUCHS), February 2, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Judith Rodin, February 13, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Jim Broadhead (FUCHS), February 14, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Reception hosted by Len and Fleur Harlan (FUCHS), February 14, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Networking and Cultivation Event for Young Alumni (FUCHS), February 15, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Investment Committee Meeting, February 15, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Pillsbury Boat Cruise (FUCHS), February 16, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Dick Loynd and Laura Toy (FUCHS), February 16, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Ronay and Richard Menschel, February 17, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Dinner and Rec. hosted by Al and Betsey Harris (FUCHS), February 17, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Checkerboard Interview, February 17, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Paul Gould, February 18, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Sr. Class Campaign Kickoff Reception, February 25, 2014 (Box 7)
  - PCCW Annual Meeting Dinner, February 28, 2014 (Box 7)
  - A Tribute to Major Rick Gannon II ‘95, March 30, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Ann Bowers, April 1, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Jim and Becky Morgan, April 1, 2014 (Box 7)
  - CSV14, April 1, 2014 (Box 7)
  - CSV Advisors Lunch, April 1, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Phone call with Fred Dombrose, April 4, 2014 (Box 7)
  - CATN Phone calls, April 8, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Tower Club Reception, April 9, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with Bill Priest, April 10, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Greeberg/Starr Professorship Luncheon, April 10, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Roy Park, April 17, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Phone call with Steve and Evalyn Milman, April 17, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Courtesy Visit with Earl Lewis, April 23, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Mellon Foundation Lecture (FUCHS), April 23, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Mellon Foundation Dinner (FUCHS), April 23, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Meeting with John Dyson, April 24, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Cornell Family Fellows Reception, April 25, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Semester Prize Lunch, May 12, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Teagle Foundation Annual Board Dinner, May 15, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Lunch with Ratan Tata, May 23, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Photo with the MOK Family, May 25, 2014 (Box 7)
  - ’39, ’44, ’49 Combined Reception, June 5, 2014 (Box 7)
  - DVM Welcome Reception, June 5, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’74 Town Hall Meeting, June 6, 2014 (Box 7)
  - CALS Launch of SIPS, June 6, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Olin Lecture, June 6, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Olin Luncheon, June 6, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’64 Dinner, June 6, 2014 (Box 7)
  - CUCALA Reception, June 6, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’79 Dinner (FUCHS), June 6, 2014 (Box 7)
  - State of the University Address, June 7, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’59 Reception, June 7, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Law School Dinner Honoring Dean Schwab, June 7, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Class of ’54 Dinner, June 7, 2014 (Box 7)
  - Cornelliana Night, June 7, 2014 (Box 7)
  - NYC Tech Campus Forum (FUCHS), June 7, 2014 (Box 7)